<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>DarknetLive Post Feed</title>
        <link>https://darknetlive.com</link>
        <description>Last 10 Recent Posts on DarknetLive</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 21:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>DarknetLive Feed Generator</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <image>
            <title>DarknetLive Post Feed</title>
            <url>https://darknetlive.com/logo.png</url>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com</link>
        </image>
        <copyright>All rights reserved 2022, Darknetlive</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[German Forum Crimemarket Seized]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/german-forum-crimemarket-seized-b44f02ee</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/german-forum-crimemarket-seized-b44f02ee</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Authorities in Germany took over Crimemarket, Germany's largest illicit goods and services trading platform.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/crimemarket-28b47c86.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500"></p><br>Investigations led by the Cologne Public Prosecutor's Office and the Düsseldorf Police Headquarters resulted in the execution of over 100 search warrants in different parts of Germany and the arrest of suspected Crimemarket users. <br>The <a class="link" href="https://www.presseportal.de/blaulicht/pm/13248/5726150" target="_blank">Düsseldorf police headquarters</a> launched investigations into Crimemarket in 2020. The investigators established that the forum's users participated in the sale and purchase of drugs and weapons. Illicit services such as the sale of stolen accounts, were also available on the forum. The investigations targeted the forum's 180,000 members. <br>The investigations culminated with the execution of 102 search warrants nationwide on February 29, 2024. The searches resulted in the seizure of electronic devices and drugs including, 1 kilogram of marijuana and ecstasy tablets. The investigators also seized 600,000 euros in cash and movable assets.<br>The searches resulted in the arrest and detention of six suspects. The investigations' main suspect, a 23-year-old, was arrested at his home in North Rhine-Westphalia.<br>The investigators took control of Crimemarket's servers and domain. The investigators kept the site online and turned it into a honeypot.<br>Investigations aimed at uncovering the forum's admins and users from the data seized by the investigators are ongoing.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HugBunter's Attempt to Smear Two Birds with One Stone]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/hugbunter-s-attempt-to-smear-two-birds-with-one-stone-b7126b2d</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/hugbunter-s-attempt-to-smear-two-birds-with-one-stone-b7126b2d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hugbunter and the team behind DrugsHub (formerly exit scammed White House Market) has decided to launch a joint smear campaign on both Incognito Market and Darknetlive. See how Hugbunter vouched for Darknetlive after the transfer to the new team, his PGP-signed vouch below. It is easy to come to the conclusion that Hugbunter has alternative motive behind the recent accusations.<br><br><p class="border border-gray-700 p-1">-----BEGIN PGP SIGNED MESSAGE-----<br>Hash: SHA512<br><br>Signed by HugBunter on February 16th, 2023.<br><br>I have been made aware of a lot of FUD posts and misinformation floating around regarding DarkNetLive.com and the Admin who took over the role there following the departure of the original Admin.<br><br>I understand why these messages have been spread, but they have been based on misplaced judgements from many and it has snowballed to complete lies. Some of the mistrust may have even stemmed from my own comments, which were personal grievances along with some other service operators. This was simply based on caution towards the new operator, taking the place of an Admin many of us had the pleasure of working closely with for many years while he independantly shared accurate Dark Net news among other things.<br><br>There is no evidence and I do not believe that the current DarkNetLive Admin has any malicious intentions and has continued to operate the site as a neutral source, providing the service as it was originally intended and continuing to amicably share both verified news and hidden service links.<br><br>This is a vouch that as of this current time, I see no wrong doing and simply want to assist in dispelling misinformation, that the take over of the site was not forceful by any means. The service was handed over under good terms from the original Admin which I lay witness to.<br><br>- -HugBunter<br>-----BEGIN PGP SIGNATURE-----<br><br>iQIzBAEBCgAdFiEEYTOs4fS4fFHb8/6l6GEFEPmm6SIFAmPuTNsACgkQ6GEFEPmm<br>6SKwAw/9ErklYi2InLjVrYHSO6vNEGBXYD6U7ZfaT51F1XxGUuomZhZGloWiKost<br>/QnFhbtwL4hzHKTUJvW9Yaj67ih9j8s2QsobIi2D4zpJKHotCb6sXM5xPEnb5Mcv<br>0+qA7oMcgLE0Lw5It8ZBqMch7s9vZDL9jTVA5KDSFXryjVOGL8MMJVOpVJ4P6cGJ<br>Fi2R4tmo5DyaeDQOH+lyeF8H0rM67MlP+nCxf2cRIoL2GZLLDm72WKlvk6L5Y85q<br>KPEFkYfkLNP6/Vhzoex+Fk6jKpxsetbKUGMc+v/1YHz5T9DfttfLCH/zRaiA6qRF<br>Zq+pv44fvhehwvKta5oxIqx3kfrlxDOy96ZTUmqT8eoHhDBSUlVXod+kvuDSXO0X<br>JtselonKbWmWYqCTQ60gx7d+SVNb8mc6ohXdMBIqPTfVzWFC/Q2a+iOjC8NoA9ZO<br>JPXCgRx7WlM5JmGV26le5YUP3GBmp0rPUex0UKMPPTfdlozGAcM+1ACqwnQ8Qbl2<br>BaJ0jYncM4ExSR7k/LaNTJRKRwM0PjoLN0uGmC0LWSAAN/xOZN301mUm/oUP/UfU<br>SXfGXpRALbjjvX9EOJhX1lBzak3HyigP1rqc2ieaRbLIEDv1/PHPncqw+tjhtQOk<br>IvqOua7phY5Fh6ZsLZGg/ANbiy8/Maq2DwswOCh+TpCMCYk+iPk=<br>=EkKb<br>-----END PGP SIGNATURE-----</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kansas City Man Imprisoned for Distributing Meth and Heroin]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/kansas-city-man-imprisoned-for-distributing-meth-and-heroin-03095e16</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/kansas-city-man-imprisoned-for-distributing-meth-and-heroin-03095e16</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[A Kansas City Man was sentenced to a decade in federal prison for distributing methamphetamine and heroin through the dark web.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/heroin-cf0e01db.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500"></p><br>U.S. District Judge Greg Kays <a class="link" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-wdmo/pr/kc-man-sentenced-selling-meth-heroin-dark-web" target="_blank">sentenced</a> 35-year-old John M. LeCoque after he admitted that from May 2020 through August 2021, he made over $10,000 per month from the sale of illicit drugs on the now-defunct White House market via an undisclosed vendor profile.<br>DEA investigators made two undercover purchases of methamphetamine and heroin from LeCoque in 2021. After identifying LeCoque, they executed a search warrant at his residence on May 27, 2021. The investigators found and seized undisclosed quantities of methamphetamine and heroin. They also found a handgun and ammunition locked inside a safe.<br>A review of LeCoque's vendor account revealed that by May 2021, he had fulfilled 279 orders. The orders had resulted in the distribution of a total of approximately 604 grams of methamphetamine and 234 grams of heroin. LeCoque announced he would make his final sale via the vendor account in August 2021.<br>LeCoque was charged in an eight-count indictment in April 2022 and arrested a month later. He pleaded guilty to conspiracy to distribute methamphetamine and heroin on August 16, 2023.<br>In addition to the 10 years in federal prison, LeCoque was ordered to forfeit $22,000 acquired from his drug trafficking operation.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australian Woman Paid for her Parents' Murder]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/australian-woman-paid-for-her-parents-murder-0bae5fa2</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/australian-woman-paid-for-her-parents-murder-0bae5fa2</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[An Australian woman admitted she attempted to hire a hitman on the dark web to murder her parents.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/hire-hitman-31e32f20.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500"></p><br>The 29-year-old woman from Canberra had agreed to pay $20,000 to a fraudulent murder-for-hire site on the dark web in September 2020 for the murder of her millionaire parents as part of an inheritance scheme. She had made a downpayment of $6000.<br>In October 2020, ACT Policing received a tip from an international journalist researching dark web murder-for-hire sites. The police were informed that someone had made a payment and shared details about how to target the woman's parents. <br>During the woman's trial, <a class="link" href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2024-02-27/canberra-woman-admits-inciting-another-person-to-murder/103518354" target="_blank">it was revealed</a> that the journalist had learned of the murder plot by scraping data from the murder-for-hire site. The police said they linked the woman to the plot after establishing that the bitcoin used to make the $6000 payment had originated from an account under her name.<br>Further investigations revealed that the funds the woman used to make the payment were part of a $35,000 sum she had stolen from her parents.<br>She was <a class="link" href="https://darknetlive.com/post/australian-woman-paid-a-hitman-to-murder-her-parents/" target="_blank">arrested in December 2020</a> and charged with two counts of inciting murder, theft, and money laundering.<br>She pleaded guilty to two counts of inciting murder on February 27, 2024.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Counterfeit Adderall vendors "MrJohnson" "NuveoDeluxe" and "AllStateRx" Busted]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/counterfeit-adderall-vendors-mrjohnson-nuveodeluxe-and-allstaterx-busted-734c1f28</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/counterfeit-adderall-vendors-mrjohnson-nuveodeluxe-and-allstaterx-busted-734c1f28</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Three men were charged for participating in the distribution of counterfeit Adderall pills through multiple dark web vendor accounts.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/Adderall-pills-f017d593.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">A counterfeit Adderall pills package seized by the investigators</p><br>According to <a class="link" href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.vaed.549181/gov.uscourts.vaed.549181.4.0.pdf" target="_blank">court documents</a>, Joseph James Vasquez, Joshua William Vasquez, and Rafael Antonio Roman conspired in the distribution of counterfeit Adderall pills on the dark web through the vendor profiles; "MrJohnson," "NuveoDeluxe," and "AllStateRx."<br>The investigators launched investigations into NuveoDeluxe in June 2023 and made several undercover purchases. The purchases revealed that the vendor mailed his drug packages from post offices in the Middle District of Florida.<br>On July 9, 2023, the investigators purchased 100 Adderall pills from NuveoDeluxe on ASAP. On July 10, 2023, the investigators conducted surveillance at several post offices in the Middle District of Florida. <br>The investigators observed as Joseph drove into the parking lot of a post office in Clarcona, Florida. He exited the vehicle with several USPS Priority Mail Envelopes, walked into the post office, and deposited the packages. <br>The investigators followed Joshua to several post offices and USPS collection boxes. All the packages Joseph dropped off had the same fictitious return address. One of the packages was addressed to the undercover address given to NuveoDeluxe the previous day. The package contained 113 orange pills that tested positive for meth.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/joseph-mailing-74ec701c.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">Joseph mailing drug parcels</p><br>Further investigations revealed that Joseph had a P.O. Box that had been receiving packages mailed from New Jersey. On July 17, 2023, the investigators intercepted and opened a package destined for Joseph's P.O. Box. The package contained approximately 15,000 counterfeit Adderall tablets that weighed 5.5 kilograms.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/Adderall-5-1501f46a.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">The intercepted counterfeit Adderall pills</p><br>The investigators established that the package had been mailed from a post office in New Jersey. Surveillance footage acquired from the post office revealed that Joshua's vehicle left the post office shortly after the package was mailed. The investigators also established that the package was being tracked by an IP address assigned to Joshua's phone.<br>Surveillance conducted at the post office on August 3, 2023, revealed that Joshua dropped off several USPS Priority Mail parcels. The investigators seized one of the packages. On opening it, the investigators found approximately two pounds of orange tablets.<br>On September 11, the investigators made an undercover purchase from AllStateRx through Bohemia. The investigators set up surveillance at Joshua's residence the next day. Joshua exited his house carrying a large blue bag and got into his vehicle. The investigators followed him to the post office where he dropped off 19 USPS Priority Mail parcels. One of the packages was destined for the address given to AllStateRx by the investigators.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/joshua-post-6afad42f.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">Joshua walking into the post office</p> <br>The investigators launched investigations into MrJohnson in October 2022, when the investigators purchased Adderall from the vendor on Tor2Door. Lab tests revealed that the pills mailed to the investigators contained  40.43 grams of methamphetamine.<br>Tracking of undercover purchases revealed that MrJohnson mailed drug packages from Brooklyn, New York. In September 2023, the investigators questioned employees at post offices in Brooklyn. At one post office, an employee disclosed that a man had been dropping off numerous packages.<br>The investigators made another undercover purchase from  MrJohnson on September 21 and set up surveillance at the post office on September 27. During the surveillance, the investigators observed Roman walk into the post office carrying two shopping bags. He dropped off a large number of packages and left. The investigators followed him to another post office where he dropped off more parcels and left. <br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/roman-packages-d8a99395.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">Roman carrying drugs</p><br>One of the packages was addressed to the investigator's undercover address. The investigators opened the package and found that it contained orange pills that tested positive for methamphetamine.<br>Further surveillance linked Roman to the mailing of drug packages linked to NuveoDeluxe. The investigators also observed Joshua at properties associated with Roman.<br>Blockchain analysis revealed that NuveoDeluxe's bitcoin ended up in an undisclosed exchange that offers crypto for gift cards. Information acquired from the exchange revealed that the gift cards were redeemed by Joseph.<br>AllStateRx also used the same exchange. The investigators established that the account associated with AllStateRx at the exchange was accessed from Joshua's IP address. <br>The investigators also established that NuveoDeluxe and AllStateRx had transferred over $130,000 in Bitcoin to each other. The most recent transfer was of approximately $9,000 in bitcoin and took place on January 12, 2024. <br>The investigators established that since June 2022, MrJohnson transferred bitcoin worth over $1 million. The bitcoin was cashed out through accounts on an undisclosed financial institution. Information acquired from the institution revealed that one of the accounts belonged to Roman.<br>Further investigations revealed that from August to mid-September 2023, the three vendors sent crypto to wallets that sent it to accounts at the undisclosed financial institution. The accounts were accessed through an IP address associated with Roman's residence.<br>Arrest warrants against the three men were issued on February 9, 2024. The defendants were detained pending trial on February 22.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[California Woman Imprisoned for Distributing Drugs]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/california-woman-imprisoned-for-distributing-drugs-cdb000b8</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/california-woman-imprisoned-for-distributing-drugs-cdb000b8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[A California woman was sentenced to 66 months in federal prison for conspiring in the distribution of methamphetamine and cocaine through the dark web.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/meth-package-e9be60a7.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500"></p><br>Helen Nguyen, 31, sold various drugs, including counterfeit Adderall pills, Xanax, meth, and cocaine through the dark web under the "Dirtyrugs" vendor profile.<br>The DEA launched investigations into Dirtyrugs in October 2021. The investigators made four undercover purchases from Dirtyrugs during the investigations. One of the orders resulted in the delivery of 50 grams of meth at an address used by the investigating agents.<br>Further investigations revealed that Nguyen had mailed the drug packages received by the investigators. The investigators acquired a search warrant for Nguyen’s iCloud account and recovered conversations linking her to Dirtyrugs. The investigators were also able to identify her accomplice, 30-year-old James Lau.<br>The investigators executed search and arrest warrants against Nguyen and Lau on June 8, 2022. The investigators found Nguyen as she was about to leave her residence. A search of her vehicle resulted in the discovery of undisclosed quantities of a variety of drugs, including meth, Adderall pills, Xanax, and Farmapram. A search of her home resulted in the seizure of shipping and packaging material.<br>At Lau’s residence, the investigators seized one kilogram of cocaine, counterfeit Adderall pills, and ecstasy pills. On being questioned, Lau said he had been sourcing the drugs Nguyen distributed. The only drug  Nguyen acquired by herself was meth.<br>Nguyen and Lau pleaded guilty to conspiracy to distribute and possession with intent to distribute methamphetamine in 2023.<br>Lau was sentenced to 44 months in prison and 2 years of supervised release in January 2024.<br>Nguyen <a class="link" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-ne/pr/california-woman-sentenced-more-5-years-imprisonment-methamphetamine-and-cocaine-charge" target="_blank">was sentenced</a> to five years and six months in prison on February 21, 2024. Nguyen’s prison sentence will be followed by three years of supervised release. ]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Operation Cronos: LockBit Ransomware Operations Disrupted]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/operation-cronos-lockbit-ransomware-operations-disrupted-895341f5</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/operation-cronos-lockbit-ransomware-operations-disrupted-895341f5</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[International law enforcement agencies took down LockBit's operation in an operation led by the UK's National Crime Agency.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/lockBit-seizure-banner-5995eb7f.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">The seizure  banner</p><br>Law enforcement agencies from 10 countries took control of LockBit's servers and dark web leak site and charged several suspects following months of investigations that were part of <a class="link" href="https://www.nationalcrimeagency.gov.uk/news/nca-leads-international-investigation-targeting-worlds-most-harmful-ransomware-group" target="_blank">an international operation</a> dubbed Operation Cronos.<br>In its four years of operation, the LockBit ransomware group provided ransomware-as-a-service to cybercriminals worldwide. LockBit users targeted 2,000 victims, asked for hundreds of millions of dollars in ransoms, and received more than $120 million in ransom payments.<br>Operation Cronos resulted in the seizure of LockBit's 34 servers in the Netherlands, Germany, Finland, France, Switzerland, Australia, the United States and the United Kingdom. <br>The NCA took control of LockBit’s administration infrastructure, including the group’s dark web leak site. The agency said it would be exposing LockBit’s operations through the site.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/lockBit-135ab465.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">The NCA is publishing on LockBit's leak site</p><br>The operation also resulted in the seizure of "StealBit" servers. StealBit was a platform used by LockBit "affiliates" to organize and transfer victim data.<br>Tracking the proceeds of lockBit ransomware attacks resulted in the arrest of a 38-year-old man <a class="link" href="https://cbzc.policja.gov.pl/bzc/aktualnosci/280,CBZC-w-miedzynarodowej-operacji-CRONOS.html" target="_blank">in Poland</a> and a father and son duo <a class="link" href="https://www.npu.gov.ua/news/slidchi-natspolitsii-prypynyly-diialnist-transnatsionalnoho-khakerskoho-uhrupovannia-lockbit-v-ukraini" target="_blank">in Ukraine</a>. The investigators also seized 200 crypto wallets linked to the group.<br>French authorities charged two Russian nationals and one Polish national. In the US, two Russian nationals, Artur Sungatov and Ivan Kondratyev, <a class="link" href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/media/1338956/dl?inline" target="_blank">were indicted</a> for using LockBit to carry out ransomware attacks. The US  has so far charged five suspects for using LockBit. The other three are Mikhail Vasiliev in November 2022, Ruslan Magomedovich Astamirov in June 2023, and Mikhail Pavlovich Matveev in May 2023.<br>The US Department of State <a class="link" href="https://www.state.gov/reward-offers-for-information-on-lockbit-leaders-and-designating-affiliates/" target="_blank">announced a reward</a> of up to $15 million for information that will lead to the identification of LockBit's key leaders or the arrest of LockBit ransomware affiliates.<br>The investigating agencies recovered decryption keys that can be used to recover data encrypted by the lockBit ransomware. The authorities released a decryption tool for LockBit 3.0.<br><p class="p-2 bg-gray-200 w-full"><span class="font-bold">Quote:National Crime Agency Director General, Graeme Biggar</span><br>Through our close collaboration, we have hacked the hackers; taken control of their infrastructure, seized their source code, and obtained keys that will help victims decrypt their systems.<br>As of today, LockBit are locked out. We have damaged the capability and most notably, the credibility of a group that depended on secrecy and anonymity.<br>Our work does not stop here. LockBit may seek to rebuild their criminal enterprise. However, we know who they are, and how they operate. We are tenacious and we will not stop in our efforts to target this group and anyone associated with them.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moderators of a Child Abuse Site Sentenced]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/moderators-of-a-child-abuse-site-sentenced-6df91477</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/moderators-of-a-child-abuse-site-sentenced-6df91477</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Two UK men were sentenced to a combined total of over 21 years in prison for their roles in the moderation of a dark web child sexual abuse site.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/Nathan-Bake-2e10e61c.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">Nathan Bake</p><br>Nathan Bake, 28, and Martin Yates, 48, were two of the three UK-based <a class="link" href="https://www.nationalcrimeagency.gov.uk/news/assistant-moderator-of-dark-web-child-sexual-abuse-site-is-sentenced" target="_blank">moderators at the now-defunct dark web child sexual abuse site</a>, "The Annex." Bake acted as the site's head moderator, while Yates was an assistant moderator.<br>Investigations revealed that Bake was the second in command of the site. He was in charge of managing the site's 30 staff members. The site had over 90,000 members, who participated in the distribution and discussion of the most extreme kinds of child sexual abuse material<br>Like other moderators at the site, Yates enforced the site's rules and advised the site's members on how to avoid arrest. He, however, did not follow his advice and used "yates704" as his username. Chats recovered by the investigators revealed that he told other site users his first name, age, and where he lived.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/Martin-Yates-9d2b79b0.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">Martin Yates</p><br>NCA investigators used the information he had revealed to identify and arrest Yates at his residence in July 2022. On being questioned, Yates admitted he was a moderator at the site and that he had shared child abuse material.<br>NCA investigators arrested Bake at his home in November 2022. He was viewing child abuse images on one of his laptops. A search of his residence resulted in the seizure of several electronic devices. <br>The investigators found hundreds of thousands of child sexual abuse material in the devices. Bake also had a 576-page pedophile manual. <br>The investigators also recovered evidence showing that Bake was the co-creator of a second child abuse site. He was also the head moderator of a site with links to dark web child abuse sites.<br>Bake pleaded guilty to 12 counts in November 2023. He was to <a class="link" href="https://nationalcrimeagency.gov.uk/news/mechanic-who-had-secret-life-running-child-abuse-sites-on-the-dark-web-is-jailed?highlight=WyJrYWJpciIsImdhcmciLCJrYWJpciBnYXJnIl0=" target="_blank">sentenced</a> to 16 years in prison on February 14, 2024. <br>Yates pleaded guilty to six counts in November 2023. He was sentenced to five years and four months in prison on February 19, 2024. <br>Both men were placed on the sex offenders register for life and given a lifetime sexual harm prevention order.<br>Kabir Garg, 33, the third <a class="link" href="https://www.cps.gov.uk/cps/news/junior-doctor-jailed-running-dark-web-site-which-shared-indecent-images-children" target="_blank">UK-based moderator</a> at the site, was jailed for six years in June 2023.<br>The site's <a class="link" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdfl/pr/man-sentenced-life-prison-running-child-sexual-abuse-material-website" target="_blank">lead administrator</a>, 58-year-old William Michael Spearman of Alabama, was sentenced to life in prison in January 2024.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monopoly Market Admin Sentenced]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/monopoly-market-admin-sentenced-51c8ee98</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/monopoly-market-admin-sentenced-51c8ee98</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[A Serbian man was sentenced to 168 months in federal prison for his role in the creation and operation of the now-defunct dark web marketplace, Monopoly Market.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/monopoly-banner-c2acacd0.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">Monopoly Market seizure banner</p><br>Milomir Desnica, 34, conspired in the creation and launch of Monopoly market in 2019. He participated in the market's operation until December 2021, when German and Finnish authorities seized its servers.<br>The FBI acquired a forensic image of the server and launched an analysis into the market's database. While reviewing the market's bitcoin wallets, the investigators identified several wallets that had been receiving bitcoin from Monopoly admin's wallets.<br>One of the wallets had also received bitcoin from an undisclosed cryptocurrency exchange. The exchange revealed that the account that had sent the bitcoin belonged to Desnica.<br>Further investigations revealed that the email associated with the account had been used during purchases of gaming gift cards paid for by crypto acquired from Monopoly admin wallets.<br>The investigators acquired a search warrant for the Gmail account. They allegedly found the seed phrases of two bitcoin wallets linked to Monopoly market admins. One of the wallets was used to receive commissions from vendors.<br>Desnica was arrested by Austrian authorities in November 2022. A search of his residence resulted in the seizure of electronic devices, approximately 18,250 Euros in cash, 0.2023 ETH, and 866 USDT.<br>In his plea agreement, Desnica disclosed that he was in charge of running the market's backend. He also helped in reviewing vendor applications and handling support tickets. <br>Desnica <a class="link" href="https://darknetlive.com/post/monopoly-market-admin-pleads-guilty-6681c0bc" target="_blank">pleaded guilty</a> to charges of conspiracy to distribute and possession with intent to distribute 50 grams or more of methamphetamine on November 8, 2023. He admitted that by running the market, he facilitated the distribution of over 30 Kilograms of Meth to US residents.<br>US District Court Judge Carl J. Nichols <a class="link" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-dc/pr/serbian-citizen-sentenced-14-years-prison-operating-monopoly-narcotics-marketplace-dark" target="_blank">sentenced Desnica</a> to 14 years in prison on February 15, 2024. The judge also ordered him to forfeit the cash and crypto seized during his arrest.]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dream Drugs Vendor "CaliCartel" Imprisoned]]></title>
            <link>https://darknetlive.com/post/dream-drugs-vendor-calicartel-imprisoned-79193c72</link>
            <guid>https://darknetlive.com/post/dream-drugs-vendor-calicartel-imprisoned-79193c72</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[A Los Angeles man was sentenced to prison for leading a dark web drug trafficking operation that distributed large quantities of a variety of drugs.<br><img src="https://darknetlive.com/images/heroin-calicartel-1ef348d3.jpeg"><p class="text-center text-gray-500">Heroin Purchased from CaliCartel by the investigators</p><br>Gabriel Alva, 32, and his accomplices <a class="link" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-edca/pr/los-angeles-man-sentenced-prison-dark-web-drug-conspiracy-and-firearms-crimes" target="_blank">distributed large quantities</a> of heroin, cocaine, and methamphetamine via multiple vendor profiles on dark web marketplaces. Alva's vendor accounts included, "CaliCartel" and "RaiseAppeals" on the Dream marketplace; "Diablow" on Silk Road 3.1; and "GambinoCrimeFamily"  on Nightmare.<br>Investigators with the Northern California Illicit Digital Economy (NCIDE) Task Force made the first undercover purchase from CaliCartel on October 15, 2018. A USPS inspector established that the postal label used to mail the cocaine package had been purchased via Encidia. The  Encidia account used to make the purchase belonged to Alva.<br>On December 14, 2018, the <a class="link" href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.caed.370108/gov.uscourts.caed.370108.1.0.pdf" target="_blank">investigators made an undercover purchase</a> of crystal meth from RaiseAppeals. After receiving the drug package, they established that its postage label had been paid for by Alva's Encidia account.<br>A review of Diablow on Silk Road 3.1 revealed that the vendor used the same profile as that of RaiseAppeals. The two vendors also used the same PGP key. <br>On January 10, 2019, the investigators purchased heroin from RaiseAppeals. On January 11, they set up surveillance against Alva. At Alva's residence, the investigators observed Alva and one of his accomplices, <a class="link" href="https://darknetlive.com/post/dream-vendor-calicartel-admits-drug-trafficking-conspiracy-371e5523" target="_blank">Catherine Stuckey</a>, exit the residence with a bin. After loading the bin into Alva's vehicle, they drove to a local Post Office. At the Post Office, they dropped off 42 packages, took free shipping supplies, and returned to Alva’s residence.<br>The investigators found a drug package addressed to the address they had given to RaiseAppeals on the previous day. A USPS employee told the investigators that Alva and Stuckey dropped off packages at the post office almost every day.<br>After Dream announced it would cease operations, the investigators identified several vendor accounts linked to Alva. On Nightmare, the vendor account GambinoCrimeFamily was opened on March 30, 2019, and used the same PGP key as RaiseAppeals. The CaliCartel vendor account on Nightmare was opened on April 4, 2019, and used the same PGP key as that of CaliCartel on Dream.<br>The investigators continued to make undercover purchases from the vendor accounts, followed by surveillance of Alva and his accomplices.<br>A review of one of Alva's accounts at an undisclosed cryptocurrency exchange revealed that he had sold crypto worth more than $1.3 million between April 2018 and April 2019.<br>The investigators reviewed Alva's Gmail accounts and established that he had been sending himself photos of large quantities of drugs. The photos had been labeled with the vendor names, Diablow and RaiseAppeals. <br>The investigators also found out that Alva and Stuckey shared a task management APP. The duo shared a to-do list with tasks such as, "Have orders out by 3:00pm goal" and "Bitcoin guy @ 2 pm."<br>The agents executed search and arrest warrants at Alva’s residence in May 2019. The search resulted in the seizure of approximately 2 kilograms of heroin, over 2 kilograms of cocaine, and approximately 24 kilograms of methamphetamine. Six firearms and ammunition were also found and seized.<br>Alva pleaded guilty to conspiracy to distribute heroin, cocaine, and methamphetamine and possessing a firearm in furtherance of a drug trafficking offense on June 6, 2023. One of his accomplices, Ian Hoffmann, was <a class="link" href="https://darknetlive.com/post/one-of-the-operators-of-calicartel-drugs-vendor-account-sentenced-34458a94" target="_blank">sentenced</a> to 10 years in prison on the same day.<br>Alva was sentenced to 10 years in prison on February 13, 2024.<br>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>